purehomedecor.com 2013-08-31

# Privacy Policy

**We ensure the privacy of all our members.**  
We, Pure Home Decor, value your privacy with us. For your familiarity with our Privacy Policy, we present here an outline of the policy, which entails the process your data is collected and used by purehomedecor.com. Please read our Privacy Policy carefully. Availing the services offered by Pure Home Decor, you agree to provide your data for use by the online sales website in the process provided in this Privacy Policy.

**Members Information and Privacy**  
Ensuring your privacy at Pure Home Decor is our commitment. Whatever information you share with us is protected. We follow stringent measures to protect the confidentiality and security of the information you provide, which are stored on our systems.  
Secure Socket Layer (SSL) is the most dependable technology available today for protection of information in online sales websites. We use this technology to ensure transparency in our dealings and your privacy. Credit card and other personal information get automatically encrypted and a secure transmission of all data happens.  
Employees on duty are entitled to have access to your information to facilitate the selling-buying process and related paraphernalia. Violation of privacy and/or security policies by the employees will lead to their possible termination, civil and/or criminal prosecution, and other disciplinary action.

**Secure Shopping Experience**  
Your online personal information at Pure Home Decor is secure. This is made possible with a blend of secure commerce servers, SSL encryption technology, digital certificates, and authentication.

**Membership Registration**  
The best shopping experience is what you will enjoy with Pure Home Decor. Only members are allowed to shop at purehomedecor.com; hence, the need for registration. Feeding in your name, email address and a password is the first step towards the registration process. You will then have your personal My Account page created at Pure Home Decor visiting which you can shop, keep track of your transactions, view redeem vouchers you have earned with every purchase, redeem the credits, and more.  
When you shop for the first time at purehomedecor.com, you should enter your name, phone number, email id, billing and shipping addresses. This is followed by entering of payment details for the transaction to happen. Your order is then deemed complete and you will receive a confirmation online. The complete information you enter is secured. Only specific members and select third parties involved in fulfilling your order, have access to the information provided. You will receive a call and/or mail from our end if we have any queries related to your order.  
Records of all purchases, store credits, returns, etc. are stored at our secured database. This information is accessible to you from your My Account page. To serve you better, you may be required to provide information related to personal preferences and demographics.  
As a member of Pure Home Decor, you will receive notifications about sales offers, new services, etc. from time to time. If you do not want to be notified, you may unsubscribe for the facility.

**Cookies**  
We use web cookies to facilitate an improved shopping experience and to save you time. Cookies are little tags or small pieces of data that we place onto your web browser while you browse through our website. This enables us to recognize you each time you return and notify you on your next visit your previous activity. Cookies let us adapt our website according to your individual preferences. A customized, personalized, and convenient shopping experience is what you will enjoy every time you shop at purehomedecor.com. Cookies do not store personally identifiable information.

**Analysis and Reporting**  
purehomedecor.com values your shopping preferences and conveniences. For your enhanced shopping experience, we use a special reporting software that allows us to analyze the type and quantity of member traffic we get at Pure Home Decor. This feature capacitates us to well serve all of our members. The software provides comprehensive analytical information that is reported at purehomedecor.com only; no personal or personally identifiable information is analyzed or gathered by the reporting software.

**Server Logs**  
Shopping is easy, fast, fun, and convenient at purehomedecor.com. This is facilitated by our server logs. Every time you shop, the web browser where the shopping takes place collects certain information (mainly type of user who is using purehomedecor.com and certain browsing activities; the information statistics do not identify you personally). No matter how many times you shop during the day or throughout the month or year, the information statistics are stored in the server logs.  
Information collected generally includes the IP address of the user accessing purehomedecor.com, the type of browser (Google chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer, etc.), operating system (Windows, Mac OS, etc.), duration, date, and time of access. This information lets us understand purehomedecor.com user dynamics, i.e. how our website is being used.

**Third Party Service Providers**  
To make our online sales website operate efficiently, we may use third party service providers. Operation paraphernalia may include hosting, data analysis, email handling, providing search results and links, assistance in order fulfillment, etc. Your information provided at purehomedecor.com may be accessed by few of the service providers who are involved in the order fulfillment, transaction and shipping process. Only relevant information on a need-to-know basis is provided to the corresponding service providers.  
Exclusions Your personal information may be disclosed by Pure Home Decor only in compliance with a court order, subpoena, administrative order, governmental order, or an event related to law. At its sole discretion, Pure Home Decor considers it necessary to protect our/others's rights to avert harm to persons/property, to fight fraud and credit risk, or to put into effect/apply terms of use of purehomedecor.com. Personally identifiable information may be transferred as an asset on account of a sale/merger (including bankruptcy) involving the entire or fraction of our business. The transfer may also happen as part of a stock sale, a corporate reorganization, etc.

**Push Notifications/Alerts**  
With your consent, we may send push notifications or alerts to your mobile device regarding your purchase. You can deactivate these messages/SMS at any time by changing the notification settings on your mobile device. We confirm, not to use this information to send any promotional or other material to your mobile device.

**Change in Privacy Policy**  
Your acknowledgement to our Privacy Policy indicates that you agree to the Terms of Use. As a member of purehomedecor.com, you unreservedly agree to our Privacy Policy. If you disagree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use purehomedecor.com. Your visit and the entire transaction including any dispute that may arise over privacy are subject to this policy.  
Pure Home Decor has the right to amend or alter this Privacy Policy any time without notifying its members in advance. Changes, if any, are posted at our website and mailed to our members. This Privacy Policy pertains to all information you have provided at purehomedecor.com. Protection and security of your information is what matters to us.
